

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



https://rayco.digital



hi@rayco.digital



https://calendly.com/rayco/digital-coffee



Deurne, Netherlands

PROFILE

I have 3 years of professional experience as a web developer. Most of it is within the E-commerce, industry and education fields. I focus on full stack, but would choose back-end if I had to choose. Lately, I developed a lot in scaling architectures on Azure and Google Cloud. This also includes optimising the architecture using tools like Redis and Elasticsearch. I bring a strategic approach to my work and deliver good results in both independent and collaborative environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2021 - Present

CRAFT Education - flextime

Deurne, Brabant

Full Stack Developer

Digitalising business processes with Laravel, built their website from the ground up using Craft CMS and building various plug-ins for Moodle in PHP. Also noteworthy, I supervise 2 interns starting Jan. 2023. Before the interns, I was the only developer at CRAFT Education. I succeeded in developing well rounded products by listening, researching & testing properly. This also shows I'm capable of working solo and holding myself accountable.

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

101Media - fulltime

Deurne, Brabant

Front-end Developer

Started as an Internship, followed up with a fulltime job throughout the summer vacation. During my time here I built multiple (WordPress) websites and helped solve support tickets.

Jul 2015 - present

Royalty based - freelance

Remote

(Hometaught) 3D generalist

Home taught interest turned into a passive income. I create curated content for Valve Corporation and fulfilled submissions for indiegame studios besides my study & other jobs. 3D design skill naturally expanded into some webdesign skill.

www.artstation.com/rayco

EDUCATION

Sept 2019 - Jan. 2024

Fontys Hogeschool (BSc)

Eindhoven

Enterprise Software Engineer Applied system design to build fullstack web applications using ASP.NET Core. Created enterprise software both solo and in groups. Grades hovers between G(8) an O(10).

2016 - 2019

Gilde Opleidingen (MBO)

Venray

Apps & Media Developer

Here I first got introduced to web development and gradually learned to program OOP PHP and vanilla Javascript.

LANGUAGES

- + Dutch (First language)
- + English (Fluent)

TECH SKILLS

- + PHP
- + Javascript
- + ASP.NET Core
- + React.js & Next.js
- + Microservice architecture
- + Laravel
- + Python
- + Docker
- + Elasticsearch
- + Craft CMS
- + Azure
- + Solidity
- + HTML & CSS

SOFTSKILLS

- + Self-Control & Stress management
- + Collaboration
- + Communication
- + Flexibility
- + Problem Solving
- + Listening
- + Drive

LINKS

- + https://github.com/raycohaex
- + https://www.linkedin.com/in/rayco-haex/
- + https://www.instagram.com/raycohaex/